import { Question } from "../contestantControls";

export const jamieQuestions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the proficiency bonus for a level 5 character?",
    options: ["+5", "+2", "+3"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What is the maximum level a character can reach in 5e?",
    options: ["25", "20", "15"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Which weapon type deals the most damage in a single hit by default?",
    options: ["Greataxe", "Glaive", "Greatsword"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which armor gives a base AC of 18 but imposes disadvantage on stealth?",
    options: ["Studded leather", "Plate armor", "Chain mail"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which race has resistance to poison?",
    options: ["Gnome", "Orc", "Dwarf"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which race has darkvision and fey ancestry?",
    options: ["Tiefling", "Elf", "Dwarf"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which bard subclass grants additional magical secrets at level 6?",
    options: ["College of Creation", "College of Lore", "College of Whispers"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Which spell lets you reshape terrain to hinder enemies?",
    options: ["Transmute Rock", "Terraform", "Wall of Stone"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which rare item gives the holder saving throws on ability checks?",
    options: ["Wand of Wonder", "Stone of Good Luck", "Elven Chain"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Which 5e ability allows you to take two turns in a round?",
    options: ["Champion", "Extra Attack", "Action Surge"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Which high-level spell can replicate a lower-level spell?",
    options: ["Imitate", "Wish", "Power Surge"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Which spell allows concentration to maintain a zone that damages enemies entering it?",
    options: ["Moonbeam", "Poison Pool", "Zone of Truth"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "Which Class is known for its wild shape ability?",
    options: ["Cleric", "Ranger", "Druid"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Which magic item lets you regain spell slots once per day?",
    options: ["Mind Crystal", "Pearl of Power", "Keycharm"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "Which monster can paralyze a target with its gaze attack?",
    options: ["Spectator", "Beholder", "Medusa"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  }
];